<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>Boost Downloads</title>
    <link>http://www.boost.org/feed/download.rss</link>
    <description />
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Distributed under the Boost Software License, Version 1.0. (See accompanying file LICENSE_1_0.txt or http://www.boost.org/LICENSE_1_0.txt)</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>Boost 1.33.1</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 5 Dec 2005 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7586&amp;package_id=8041&amp;release_id=376197</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<HR>

<H3>Updated Libraries</H3>
<ul>
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="doc/html/any.html">Any Library</a>:</SPAN> Cast to reference types introduced in 1.33.0 is now documented on <CODE>any_cast</CODE> documentation page. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/config/index.html">Config Library</a>:</SPAN> Don't undef BOOST_LIB_TOOLSET after use. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/python/doc/index.html">Boost.Python</a>:</SPAN> 
<ul>
<li>The build now assumes Python 2.4 by default, rather than 2.2 
<li>Support Python that's built without Unicode support 
<li>Support for wrapping classes with overloaded address-of (<CODE>&amp;</CODE>) operators </li></ul>
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/smart_ptr/index.html">Smart Pointer Library</a>:</SPAN> Fixed problems under Metrowerks CodeWarrior on PowerPC (Mac OS X) with inlining on, GNU GCC on PowerPC 64. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/regex/doc/index.html">Regex Library</a>:</SPAN> Fixed the supplied makefiles, and other small compiler specific changes. Refer to the <a href="libs/regex/doc/history.html">regex history page</a> for more information on these and other small changes. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/iostreams/doc/index.html">Iostreams Library</a>:</SPAN> Improved the interface for accessing a chain's components, added <CODE>is_open</CODE> members to the file and file descriptor devices, fixed memory-mapped files on Windows, and made minor changes to the documentation. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/functional/hash/index.html">Functional/Hash Library</a>:</SPAN> Fixed the points example. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/multi_index/doc/index.html">Multi-index Containers Library</a>:</SPAN> Fixed a problem with multithreaded code, and other minor changes. Refer to the library <a href="libs/multi_index/doc/release_notes.html#boost_1_33_1">release notes</a> for further details. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/graph/doc/table_of_contents.html">Graph Library</a>:</SPAN> 
<ul>
<li>Fixed a problem with the relaxed heap on x86 Linux (fixes bug in <TT>dijkstra_shortest_paths</TT>). 
<li>Fixed problems with <a href="libs/graph/doc/cuthill_mckee_ordering.html"><CODE>cuthill_mckee_ordering</CODE></a> and <a href="libs/graph/doc/king_ordering.html"><CODE>king_ordering</CODE></a> producing no results. 
<li>Added <TT>color_map</TT> parameter to <TT>dijkstra_shortest_paths</TT>. </li></ul>
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/signals/doc/index.html">Signals Library</a>:</SPAN> Fixed problems with the use of Signals across shared library boundaries. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/thread/doc/index.html">Thread library</a>:</SPAN> <CODE>read_write_mutex</CODE> has been removed due to problems with deadlocks. 
<li><SPAN class=library><a href="libs/wave/index.html">Wave library</a> (V1.2.1)</SPAN> Fixed a couple of problems, refer to the <a href="libs/wave/ChangeLog">change log</a> for further details. </li></ul>
<H3>Supported Compilers</H3>
<p>Boost is tested on a wide range of compilers and platforms. Since Boost libraries rely on modern C++ features not available in all compilers, not all Boost libraries will work with every compiler. The following compilers and platforms have been extensively tested with Boost, although many other compilers and platforms will work as well. For more information, see the <a href="http://www.boost.org/regression/release/user/">regression test results</a>.</p>
<p><B>New for this release</B>: Support for building with the newest STLport-5.0 was added. The support includes building with MinGW Runtime 3.8 plus STLport-5.0 improved to support wide character operations. Apple GCC 4.0, HP Tru64 C++, and Microsoft Visual C++ 8.0 are supported platforms. We have added an experimental autoconf-like <CODE>configure</CODE> script for Unix-like systems: run <CODE>configure --help</CODE> for more information.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://developer.apple.com/">Apple GCC</a> 3.3, 4.0 on Mac OS X. 
<li><a href="http://www.borland.com/us/products/cbuilder/">Borland C++</a> 5.6.4 on Windows. 
<li><a href="http://gcc.gnu.org">GNU C++</a> 2.95.3 (with and without STLport), 3.2.x., 3.3.x, 3.4.x, 4.0.x on Windows, Linux and Solaris. 
<li><a href="http://h30097.www3.hp.com/cplus/">HP C++ for Tru64 UNIX 7.1</a>. 
<li><a href="http://www.intel.com/cd/software/products/asmo-na/eng/compilers/index.htm">Intel C++</a> 8.1, 9.0 on Windows, Linux. 
<li><a href="http://www.metrowerks.com">Metrowerks CodeWarrior</a> 8.3, 9.4, 9.5 on Mac OS X and Windows. 
<li><a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/visualc/">Microsoft Visual C++</a> 6.0 (sp5, with and without STLport), 7.0, 7.1, 8.0. Note: Boost does not support the non-standard "Safe" C++ Library shipping with Visual C++ 8.0, which may result in many spurious warnings from Boost headers and other standards-conforming C++ code. To suppress these warnings, define the macro <CODE>_SCL_SECURE_NO_DEPRECATE</CODE>. </li></ul>
<H3>Acknowledgements</H3>
<p><img class=left-inset height=118 alt="Medieval Mr. Gregor" src="/gfx/boost_1_33_0.jpg" width=128> <a href="people/doug_gregor.html">Douglas Gregor</a> managed this release.</p>
<p>A great number of people contributed their time and expertise to make this release possible. Special thanks go to Aleksey Gurtovoy and Misha Bergal, who managed to keep the regression testing system working throughout the release process; David Abrahams, Beman Dawes, Aleksey Gurtovoy, Bronek Kozicki, Rene Rivera and Jonathan Turkanis for greatly improving the quality of this release; Rene Rivera for the new Boost web page design; and Zoltan "cad" Juhasz for the new Boost logo.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost 1.33.1 Documentation</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 5 Dec 2005 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7586&amp;package_id=159715&amp;release_id=376194</link>
      <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost.Jam 3.1.12</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2006 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7586&amp;package_id=72941&amp;release_id=344791</link>
      <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost.Build 2.0-m10</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2004 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7586&amp;package_id=80982&amp;release_id=278763</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many toolsets were added: Intel, Metrowerks, Comeau, aCC, vacpp. Documentation was converted to BoostBook and improved. Performance was improved.
<ul>
<li>Toolsets initialization syntax is much more uniform. Compiler and linker flags can now be specified. </li>
<li>The algorithm for computing build properties was improved. Conditional requirements can be chained, and a number of bugs were fixed. 
<li>Specific order of properties can be specified. 
<li>The main target rules can be called from everywhere, not necessary from Jamfile. 
<li>Check for "unused sources" removed. 
<li>The &lt;library&gt; <LIBRARY>feature affects only linking now. 
<li>The &lt;file&gt; <FILE>feature now works only for libraries. 
<li>Simpler syntax for "searched" libraries was added. 
<li>New &lt;dependency&gt; <DEPENDENCY>feature.</li></ul>
<p>Unix: The right order of static libraries on Unix is automatically computed. The &lt;hardcode-dll-paths&gt; <HARDCODE-DLL-PATHS>feature is the default.</p>
<p>gcc: The -fPIC option is passed when creating shared libraries. Problems with distcc were solved.</p>
<p>Sun: It's now possible to use the sun linker (as opposed to gnu), and to compile C files.</p>
<p>Darwin: Shared libraries are now supported.</p>
<p>MSVC: Before resource files compilation, the setup script is invoked. Options deprecated in 8.0 are not longer used.</p>
<p>The following bugs were fixed:</p>
<ul>
<li>The &lt;unit-test&gt; rule did not handle the &lt;library&gt; property 
<li>Don't add "bin" to the build directory explicitly specified by the user. 
<li>Allow &lt;include-type&gt; to select staged targets, even with &lt;traverse-dependencies&gt;off. 
<li>Includes for the form '# include &lt;whatever&gt;" did not work. 
<li>(Qt) Add paths to all dependent libs to uic command line, which helps if the UI files uses plugins. 
<li>Using &lt;toolset-msvc:version&gt;xxx in requirements was broken. 
<li>Error message printed when target can be found is much more clear. 
<li>Inline targets in sources of 'stage' did not work. 
<li>Don't produce 'independent target' warnings on Windows 
<li>(gcc) The &lt;link-runtime&gt;static did not work. 
<li>(gcc) Suppress warnings from the 'ar' tool on some systems. 
<li>(gcc) Don't try to set soname on NT.</li></ul>
<p>Developer visible changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Generator priorities are gone, explicit overrides are used. 
<li>'Active' features were removed 
<li>Support for VMS paths was added.</li></ul>
<p>Thanks to Christopher Currie, Pedro Ferreira, Philipp Frauenfelder, Andre Hentz, Jurgen Hunold, Toon Knapen, Johan Nilsson, Alexey Pakhunov, Brock Peabody, Michael Stevens and Zbynek Winkler who contributed code to this release.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>