<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE library PUBLIC "-//Boost//DTD BoostBook XML V1.0//EN" "http://www.boost.org/tools/boostbook/dtd/boostbook.dtd">
<article id="boost_jam_3_1_15" name="Boost Jam 3.1.15" dirname="boost_jam_3_1_15"
last-revision="Sun, 30 Sep 2007 16:27:00 GMT" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude">
  <articleinfo>
    <authorgroup>
    <author>
      <firstname>Rene</firstname> <surname>Rivera</surname>
    </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <articlepurpose>
      This release sees a variety of fixes for long standing Perforce/Jam problems.
      Most of them relating to running actions in parallel with the -jN option. The
      end result of the changes is that running parallel actions is now reliably
      possible in Unix and Windows environments. Many thanks to Noel for joining
      the effort, to implement and fix the Unix side of stuff.
    </articlepurpose>
  </articleinfo>
  <title>Boost Jam 3.1.15</title>
  <para>
    <download><![CDATA[http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=7586&package_id=72941&release_id=543223]]></download>
  </para>
  <para>
    This release sees a variety of fixes for long standing Perforce/Jam problems.
    Most of them relating to running actions in parallel with the -jN option. The
    end result of the changes is that running parallel actions is now reliably possible
    in Unix and Windows environments. Many thanks to Noel for joining the effort,
    to implement and fix the Unix side of stuff.
  </para>
  <itemizedlist>
    <listitem>
      Add support for building bjam with pgi and pathscale toolsets. -- Noel B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Implement running action commands through pipes (-p option) to fix jumbled
      output when using parallel execution with -j option. This is implemented for
      Unix variants, and Windows (Win32/NT). -- Rene R., Noel B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add &quot;sun&quot; as alias to Sun Workshop compiler tools. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Set MAXLINE in jam.h to 23k bytes for AIX. The piecemeal archive action was
      broken with the default MAXLINE of 102400. Because the AIX shell uses some
      of the 24k default buffer size for its own use, I reduced it to 23k. -- Noel
      B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Make use of output dir options of msvc to not polute src dir with compiled
      files. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      A small fix, so -d+2 will always show the &quot;real&quot; commands being executed
      instead of casually the name of a temporary batch file. -- Roland S.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add test to check 'bjam -n'. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add test to check 'bjam -d2'. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Bring back missing output of -n option. The -o option continues to be broken
      as it has been for a long time now because of the @ file feature. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Update GC support to work with Boehm GC 7.0. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Revert the BOOST_BUILD_PATH change, since the directory passed to boost-build
      should be first in searched paths, else project local build system will not
      be picked correctly. The order had been changed to allow searching of alternate
      user-config.jam files from boost build. This better should be done with --user-config=
      switch or similar. -- Roland S.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Initial support for defining action body from Python. -- Vladimir P.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Implement @() expansion during parse phase. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Define OSPLAT var unconditionally, and more generically, when possible. --
      Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Fix undeclared INT_MAX on some platforms, i.e. Linux. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Modified execunix.c to add support for terminating processes that consume too
      much cpu or that hang and fail to consume cpu at all. This in support of the
      bjam -lx option. -- Noel B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add internal dependencies for multi-file generating actions to indicate that
      the targets all only appear when the first target appears. This fixes the long
      standing problem Perforce/Jam has with multi-file actions and parallel execution
      (-jN). -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add test of -l limit option now that it's implemented on windows and unix.
      -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add test for no-op @() expansion. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Handle invalid formats of @() as doing a straight substitution instead of erroring
      out. -- Rene R.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Various fixes to compile on SGI/Irix. -- Noel B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add output for when actions timeout with -lN option. -- Rene R., Noel B.
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      Add needed include (according to XOPEN) for definition of WIFEXITED and WEXITSTATUS.
      -- Markus S.
    </listitem>
  </itemizedlist>
</article>
